<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<bbw>
	<news>
		<newsItem id="1" title="Sleep Therapy" image_thumb="Slide1_thumb.jpg" image_large="Slide1.jpg" source="Charlotte Magazine" date="01-03-2008">
		  <description>
		  	<![CDATA[For years I&#x2019;ve been plagued by the annoying problem of not being able to fall asleep at night. I&#x2019;ve trued just about every natural option-from Sleepytime tea and journaling to no caffeine after 6 p.m. - all to no avail. Nothing, it seemed, could bring a restful night&#x2019;s sleep-until I tried aromatherapy. <strong>Bath &amp; Body Works&#x2019; Aromatherapy Sleep Collection</strong> was designed with the hlep of one of the world&#x2019;s most renowned sleep experts, Dr. Michael J. Breus. The premise is simple: the blend of essential oils (in this case, vanilla absolute and chamomile) eases you into sleep mode. Every night before bed I sprayed my pillow and bed sheets with the vanilla-infused pillow mist and lathered my hands with the lotion. Within minutes of head-to-pillow, I was fast asleep. Call in mental, but it worked for me. Even when I was sure I would hit REM mode without help, I still spritzed and sprayed simply because the scent was so subtle yet intoxicating. Maybe it was the idea that a sleep aid could be in the form of a spritz rather than a pill that piqued my interest-but either way, the result was seven hours of nice, long sleep. -B. M.]]>
		  </description>
		</newsItem>
	
		<newsItem id="2" title="The Sweet Escape" image_thumb="ebonySlide1_thumb.jpg" image_large="ebonySlide1.jpg" source="Ebony Magazine" date="01-01-2008">
		  <description>
		  	<![CDATA[When your days are filled with family matters, career concerns and never-ending to-do lists, it can be difficult to schedule some &#x201C;me time.&#x201D; But you don&#x2019;t have to head to the spa to get away from the demands of the day. Indulge in a relaxing ritual that rejuvenates your mind and body by transforming your tub into a pampering oasis. From essential oils that soak stress away to tools that massage tired muscles, these picks are guaranteed to turn your bath into bliss:<p>Essentials: Bath &amp; Body Works Aromatherapy Sleep Dream Bath</p>]]>
		  </description>
		</newsItem>
		
		<newsItem id="3" title="Achieve a stunning glow from head to toe" image_thumb="essence_thumb.jpg" image_large="essence.JPG" source="Essence Magazine" date="01-04-2008">
		  <description>
		  	<![CDATA[<p>Achieve a stunning glow from head to toe with treats that work overtime while you sleep.</p>Sleeping Beauty: Bath &amp; Body Works Aromatherapy Pillow Mist for a seductive shortcut to sweet dreams.]]>
		  </description>
		</newsItem>
	
		<newsItem id="4" title="When you’re winding down" image_thumb="familycircle_thumb.jpg" image_large="familycircle.jpg" source="Family Circle Magazine" date="01-03-2008">
		  <description>
		  	<![CDATA[When you&#x2019;re winding down at the end of the day, let your beauty products kick into high gear: &#x201C;Your skin is most receptive to absorbing nourishing ingredients and repairing itself while you sleep,&#x201D; says Frederic Brandt, M.D., a dermatologist in New York City who put these P.M. pamperers to work on the night shift. <p> Keep Bath &amp; Body Works Aromatherapy Sleep Pillow Mist in Lavender Chamomile by your bed to ease restless nights. The snooze-inducing blend incorporates vanilla, a scent that helps quiet stimulating alpha brain waves.</p>]]>
		  </description>
		</newsItem>
	
		<newsItem id="5" title="Sleep more." image_thumb="fitnessSlide_thumb.jpg" image_large="fitnessSlide.jpg" source="Fitness Magazine" date="01-04-2008">
		  <description>
		  	<![CDATA[While you snooze, your body has a chance to repair cells and &#x201C;reset&#x201D; hormone levels, including cortisol. &#x201C;Your system can focus inward because it&#x2019;s not using up energy to think, talk and walk,&#x201D; says Jeannette Graf, M.D., a dermatologist in New York City and author of <em>Stop Aging, Start Living.</em> Aim for eight hours a night, she suggests. For help falling asleep, take a warm bath, then apply a body lotion or oil with a calming aroma, such as lavender, vanilla, rose or ylang-ylang. We like Bath &amp; Body Works Aromatherapy Sleep Body Lotion Lavender Vanilla.]]>
		  </description>
		</newsItem>
		<newsItem id="6" title="Dr. Breus and Aromatherapy Sleep Collection" image_thumb="happi1_thumb.jpg" image_large="happi1.jpg" source="Happi" date="01-02-2008">
		  <description>
		  	<![CDATA[Designed with the help of one of the world&#x2019;s most renowned sleep experts, Dr. Michael J. Breus, the new Bath &amp; Body Works Aromatherapy Sleep Collection consists of three luxurious formulas: a rich, cream bubble bath, body lotion and pillow mist. Scent selections include lavender chamomile or vanilla chamomile.]]>
		  </description>
		</newsItem>
	
		<newsItem id="7" title="Lucky Breaks" image_thumb="luckybreaks_thumb.jpg" image_large="luckybreaks.jpg" source="Lucky Magazine" date="01-05-2008">
		  <description>
		  	<![CDATA[This beauty megachain built a devoted following with its expansive range of shower gels and lotions in truly great scents like Lemongrass Sage and Blushing Cherry Blossom. The more than 1,600 stores have also recently added a number of exclusive top-notch brands to their candy-store-esque offerings, including C.O. Bigelow and Patricia Wexler M.D. Dermatology, plus a well-edited selection of products from Frederick Fekkai, Molton Brown, Ahava, and more.]]>
		  </description>
		</newsItem>
	
		<newsItem id="8" title="Enhance the calming effect of scent with a pampering treat" image_thumb="parenting_thumb.jpg" image_large="parenting.jpg" source="Parenting" date="01-07-2008">
		  <description>
		  	<![CDATA[Enhance the calming effect of scent with a pampering treat. Try: Aromatherapy Sleep Body Lotion in Lavender Chamomile.]]>
		  </description>
		</newsItem>
		
		<newsItem id="10" title="Sleep Smell" image_thumb="express_thumb.jpg" image_large="express.jpg" source="Washington Post Express" date="12-10-2007">
		  <description>
		  	<![CDATA[<p>Aromatherapy hasn&#x2019;t even run true for us, for whom the sense of smell has but two purposes; to detect the presence of food and to detect whether milk has gone bad. But we&#x2019;re willing to buy that, for some, a hearty spray of Bath &amp; Body Works&#x2019; lightly sweet (and slightly cloying) vanilla - chamomile <em>Sleep Pillow Mist</em> could seem soothing, especially if one&#x2019;s bedroom has an unpleasant odor, perhaps because one owns a terrible cat. Its companion, <em>Sleep Body Lotion</em>, is similarly light; we enjoyed the bracing lavender chamomile.
            </p>]]>
		  </description>
		</newsItem>

		<newsItem id="11" title="What&#x2019;s the perfect bedroom temp?" image_thumb="cosmo_thumb.jpg" image_large="cosmo.jpg" source="Cosmopolitan" date="01-02-2008">
		  <description>
		  	<![CDATA[<p>What&#x2019;s the perfect bedroom temp? Prepare your boudoir by setting your thermostat between 67 and 72 degrees. &#x201C;It&#x2019;s the best temperature to keep your skin healthy and hydrated,&#x201D; says Michael Breus, PhD, author of <em>Beauty Sleep</em>.</p><br/><p>Pillow Talk. Sleep on a satin pillowcase can prevent wrinkles. &#x201C;But if you have pimple-prone skin, it&#x2019;s actually a smart idea to stick with to a cotton, since it soaks up sweat and oil better than silky fabrics do," says Breus.</p>]]>
		  </description>
		</newsItem>
		
		<newsItem id="12" title="Look What We Found!" image_thumb="oprah_thumb.jpg" image_large="oprah.jpg" source="O Magazine" date="May 2008">
		  <description>
		  	<![CDATA[<p>Roll-On Remedies</p><p>When <b>Bath &amp; Body Works</b> sent Katie its new <b>Instant Aromatherapy Blends</b>, she started testing them immediately. As soon as her familiar postlunch slump hit, she reached for <b>Energy Boost</b>. Ten minutes later, she had reorganized her cubicle, returned three phone-calls, finished Val’s expense report, and filled Jenny in on industry gossip. Was it the aromatherapy? She’s not positive. But she hadn’t felt that dynamic in weeks.</p>
		  ]]>
		  </description>
		</newsItem>

	
	</news>


	<raves>

		<raveItem id="1" title="Love it" image="2966729.png" image1="2966729b.png" poster="Fordgirl" storeURL="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3366913&cp=3294363" clickTagUrl="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3319964&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Sleep-_-Lavender%20Chamomile%20Pillow%20Mist" shopNowTag="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3366913&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Sleep-_-Shop%20Now%20Lavender%20Chamomile%20Pillow%20Mist" product="Pillow Mist - Sleep - Lavender Chamomile" from="Buffalo, NY">
		  <description>	
			<![CDATA[I love this product. It smells fantastic, I could use it as a body spray it smells so good. Perfect scent for pillows and sheets. I do have an easier time falling asleep using this product. I would reccommend it to everyone.]]>
		  </description>
		</raveItem>

		<raveItem id="2" title="I love to pamper myself" image="dream.png" image1="dreamb.png" poster="redhair" storeURL="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3395516&cp=3294363" clickTagUrl="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3395516&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Reviews-_-Lavender%20Vanilla%20Dream%20Bath" shopNowTag="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3395516&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Reviews-_-Lavender%20Vanilla%20Dream%20Bath" product="Dream Bath - Sleep - Lavender Vanilla" from="Washington State">
		  <description>
			<![CDATA[I love this product. I use it once a week to help destress. Also use the pillow mist and sleep lotion. Which I love. I have recomended this product to my friends.]]>
		  </description>
		</raveItem>

		<raveItem id="3" title="Stamina! Stamina!" image="2922073.png" image1="2922073b.png" poster="LimitedMan" storeURL="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3367475&cp=3294363" clickTagUrl="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3319976&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Instant%20Aromatherapy-_-Stamina%20Boost" shopNowTag="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3367475&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Instant%20Aromatherapy-_-Shop%20Now%20Stamina%20Boost" product="Instant Aromatherapy - Stamina Boost" from="Delaware, OH">
		  <description>
			<![CDATA[This works well for me! I love the scent that it has because as a guy I don't want to wear lady scents. This is not one of them! It is a clean and refreshing scent for both men and women. It also works because I was at work and needed a little push to get some more work done and I was able to after following the instructions on the box! I was able to pick up and go! This is a good collection!]]>
		  </description>
		</raveItem>

		<raveItem id="4" title="Every bubble bath lover should have this!" image="orange_ginger_luxury_bath_sm.png" image1="orange_ginger_luxury_bath_lg.png" poster="Severess" storeURL="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3395515&cp=3294363" clickTagUrl="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3395515&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Reviews-_-Orange%20Ginger%20Luxury%20Bath" shopNowTag="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3395515&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Reviews-_-Orange%20Ginger%20Luxury%20Bath" product="Luxury Bath - Energy - Orange Ginger" from="Hobbs, NM">
		  <description>
			<![CDATA[AMAZING! This is probably the best bubble bath I've ever had! Unlike most bubble bath, this is rich and thick and the bubbles last forever. It only takes a capful and you have a luxurious, heavenly scented bath. I'm on-line right now to buy another bottle in case it sells out!]]>
		  </description>
		</raveItem>

		<raveItem id="5" title="Great for restless sleepers" image="2966728.png" image1="2966728b.png" poster="irshiz" storeURL="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3395517&cp=3294363" clickTagUrl="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3395517&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Reviews-_-Lavender%20Vanilla%20Pillow%20Mist" shopNowTag="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3395517&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Reviews-_-Lavender%20Vanilla%20Pillow%20Mist" product="Pillow Mist - Sleep - Lavender Vanilla" from="Iowa">
		  <description>
			<![CDATA[I love this stuff!!! I have a hard time falling to sleep & staying asleep at night but with Lavender Vanilla I find myself having a great nights rest...You just get a feeling of being snuggled. My whole body just relaxes and I drift off. Secretly I think my husband enjoys it also because he seems to sleep more peacefully.]]>
		  </description>
		</raveItem>
		
		
		<raveItem id="6" title="THE BEST YOU CAN GET!!!!" image="2906769.png" image1="2906769b.png" poster="Dilia" storeURL="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3395518&cp=3294363" clickTagUrl="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3395518&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Reviews-_-Black%20Currant%20Vanilla%20Sugar%20Scrub" shopNowTag="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3395518&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Reviews-_-Black%20Currant%20Vanilla%20Sugar%20Scrub" product="Sugar Scrub - Sensuality - Black Currant Vanilla" from="Colorado">
		  <description>
			<![CDATA[This is the best scrub i have ever tried in my entire life! i have dry skin but after using this product my skin feels like i was just born again! the scent is amazing - the entire house fills up with it after i bath. and it is the sexiest scent ever! highly recommended!]]>
		  </description>
		</raveItem>
		
		
		<raveItem id="7" title="Brilliant Aroma!!" image="2922066.png" image1="2922066b.png" poster="DianaLovesLovely" storeURL="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3395519&cp=3294363" clickTagUrl="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3395519&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Reviews-_-Lavender%20Chamomile%20Hand%20Soap" shopNowTag="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3395519&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Reviews-_-Lavender%20Chamomile%20Hand%20Soap" product="Hand Soap - Sleep - Lavender Chamomile" from="WA">
		  <description>
			<![CDATA[I've stocked up my bathroom cupboard with these Aromatherapy hand soaps and I've got almost all scents in this line. I put each of Sleep, Stress Relief, Energy and Sensual soaps by the bathroom sink, and I use it in accordance with my moods. This Lavender Chamomile has the most relaxing, calming and comforting aroma of all, so I always use this right before I go to bed. It helps me sleep peacefully every night. I love it and so does my husband!!]]>
		  </description>
		</raveItem>
	</raves>


<carousel>
		<thumbnail filename="Sleep.swf" asset="sleep" image_circle="Sleep_Circle.swf">
			<header>GET A BETTER NIGHT'S SLEEP</header>
			<subtext>Did you know 75% of adults report sleep difficulties?</subtext>
			<product_1>
				<image>Sleep1.swf</image>
				<description header="LAVENDER CHAMOMILE LUXURY BATH"  url="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3319962&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Sleep-_-Lavender%20Chamomile%20Luxury%20Bath" subtext="">Sleep well. Lavender Essential Oil soothes and calms so you can sleep better. Chamomile Essential Oil has a lulling effect to enhance sleep. This luxurious cream bath contains Aloe to nourish and rejuvenate skin.</description>
				<shop_now><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3366911&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Sleep-_-Shop%20Now%20Lavender%20Chamomile%20Luxury%20Bath]]></shop_now>
				<view_all><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3366917&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Sleep-_-View%20All%20Sleep]]></view_all>
			</product_1>
			<product_2>
				<image>Sleep2.swf</image>
				<description header="LAVENDER CHAMOMILE BODY LOTION" url="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3319963&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Sleep-_-Lavender%20Chamomile%20Body%20Lotion" subtext="">Sleep well. Lavender Essential Oil soothes and calms so you can sleep better. Chamomile Essential Oil has a lulling effect to enhance sleep. This ultra-creamy body lotion contains Natural Soybean Oil to nourish and moisturize skin, and Glycerin to attract moisture to skin.</description>
				<shop_now><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3366912&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Sleep-_-Shop%20Now%20Lavender%20Chamomile%20Body%20Lotion]]></shop_now>
				<view_all><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3366917&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Sleep-_-View%20All%20Sleep]]></view_all>
			</product_2>
			<product_3>
				<image>Sleep3.swf</image>
				<description header="LAVENDER CHAMOMILE PILLOW MIST" url="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3319964&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Sleep-_-Lavender%20Chamomile%20Pillow%20Mist" subtext="">Lavender Essential Oil soothes and calms you so you can sleep better. Chamomile Essential Oil has a lulling effect to enhance sleep. Spray a light mist over the pillow or sheets each night before bed to have sweet dreams and wake to a renewed you.</description>
				<shop_now><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3366913&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Sleep-_-Shop%20Now%20Lavender%20Chamomile%20Pillow%20Mist]]></shop_now>
				<view_all><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3366917&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Sleep-_-View%20All%20Sleep]]></view_all>
			</product_3>
			<view_all>View All Sleep</view_all>
			
		</thumbnail>

		<thumbnail filename="Sensuality.swf" asset="sensuality" image_circle="Sensuality_Circle.swf">
			<header>AWAKEN YOUR SENSES</header>
			<subtext>Feel confident, beautiful and complete.</subtext>
			<product_1>
				<image>Sensual1.swf</image>
				<description header="BLACK CURRANT VANILLA BODY LOTION" url="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3319966&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Sensuality-_-Black%20Currant%20Vanilla%20Body%20Lotion" subtext="">Put love in the air. Black Currant Absolute inspires heightened sensuality. Vanilla Absolute soothes and calms to instill feelings of comfort. This ultra-creamy body lotion contains Natural Soybean Oil to nourish and moisturize skin, and Glycerin to attract moisture to skin.</description>
				<shop_now><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3367447&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Sensuality-_-Shop%20Now%20Black%20Currant%20Vanilla%20Body%20Lotion]]></shop_now>
				<view_all><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3367457&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Sensuality-_-View%20All%20Sensuality]]></view_all>			
			</product_1>
			<product_2>
				<image>Sensual2.swf</image>
				<description header="BLACK CURRANT VANILLA CANDLE" url="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3319967&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Sensuality-_-Black%20Currant%20Vanilla%20Scented%20Candle" subtext="">Put love in the air. Black Currant inspires heightened sensuality. Vanilla soothes, calms and instills feelings of comfort. Enjoy the candlelight and an aromatherapeutic sensory experience.</description>
				<shop_now><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3367448&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Sensuality-_-Shop%20Now%20Black%20Currant%20Vanilla%20Scented%20Candle]]></shop_now>
				<view_all><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3367457&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Sensuality-_-View%20All%20Sensuality]]></view_all>
			</product_2>
			<product_3>
				<image>Sensual3.swf</image>
				<description header="BLACK CURRANT VANILLA MASSAGE OIL" url="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3319965&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Sensuality-_-Black%20Currant%20Vanilla%20Massage%20Oil" subtext="">Put love in the air. Black Currant Absolute inspires heightened sensuality. Vanilla Absolute soothes and calms to instill feelings of comfort. This soothing oil blend contains Sunflower Oil, rich in the antioxidant Vitamin E, to moisturize skin and help keep it young-looking. Massage into freshly cleansed skin, or add to warm, running bath water for the ultimate relaxing bath.</description>
				<shop_now><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3367449&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Sensuality-_-Shop%20Now%20Black%20Currant%20Vanilla%20Massage%20Oil]]></shop_now>				
				<view_all><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3367457&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Sensuality-_-View%20All%20Sensuality]]></view_all>
			</product_3>			
			<view_all>View All Sensuality</view_all>
		</thumbnail>

		<thumbnail filename="StressRelief.swf" asset="stress_relief" image_circle="Stress_Circle.swf">
			<header>STRESS LESS</header>
			<subtext>Did you know 75%-90% of all primary care visits are for stress-related complaints?</subtext>
			<product_1>
				<image>Stress1.swf</image>
				<description header="EUCALYPTUS SPEARMINT BODY WASH" url="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3319972&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Stress%20Relief-_-Eucalyptus%20Spearmint%20Body%20Wash" subtext="">Think clearly. Eucalyptus Essential Oil clears the mind to improve concentration. Spearmint Essential Oil is uplifting and helps the mind to focus. This nourishing body wash contains Green Tea Extract to help keep skin looking younger and healthier.</description>
				<shop_now><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3367409&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Stress%20Relief-_-Shop%20Now%20Eucalyptus%20Spearmint%20Body%20Wash]]></shop_now>
				<view_all><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3367417&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Stress%20Relief-_-View%20All%20Stress%20Relief]]></view_all>			
			</product_1>
			<product_2>
				<image>Stress2.swf</image>
				<description header="EUCALYPTUS SPEARMINT BODY LOTION" url="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3319973&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Stress%20Relief-_-Eucalyptus%20Spearmint%20Body%20Lotion" subtext="">Think clearly. Eucalyptus Essential Oil clears the mind to improve concentration. Spearmint Essential Oil is uplifting and helps the mind to focus. This ultra-creamy body lotion contains Natural Soybean Oil to nourish and moisturize skin, and Glycerin to attract moisture to skin.</description>
				<shop_now><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3367410&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Stress%20Relief-_-Shop%20Now%20Eucalyptus%20Spearmint%20Body%20Lotion]]></shop_now>
				<view_all><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3367417&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Stress%20Relief-_-View%20All%20Stress%20Relief]]></view_all>
			</product_2>
			<product_3>
				<image>Stress3.swf</image>
				<description header="EUCALYPTUS SPEARMINT SCENTPORT®" url="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3319974&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Stress%20Relief-_-Eucalyptus%20Spearmint%20ScentPort" subtext="">Eucalyptus clears the mind to improve concentration. Spearmint is uplifting and helps the mind to focus. SCENTPORT® provides all-day, all-night, continuous fragrance in any room, for the most aromatherapeutic sensory fragrance experience ever!</description>
				<shop_now><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3367411&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Stress%20Relief-_-Shop%20Now%20Eucalyptus%20Spearmint%20ScentPort]]></shop_now>
				<view_all><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3367417&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Stress%20Relief-_-View%20All%20Stress%20Relief]]></view_all>
			</product_3>
			<view_all>View All Stress Relief</view_all>
		</thumbnail>

		<thumbnail filename="LimitedEdition.swf" asset="limited_edition" image_circle="LimitedEdition_Circle.swf">
			<header>LIMITED EDITIONS</header>
			<subtext>New Aromatherapy Blends with benefits</subtext>
			<product_1>
				<image>Limited1.swf</image>
				<description header="WARM MILK &amp; HONEY LUXE BATH" url="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3367500&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Limited%20Editions-_-Warm%20Milk%20%26%20Honey%20Luxe%20Bath" subtext="">Good night. Cinnamon essential oil is comforting. Clove essential oil is calming. As part of the perfect bedtime ritual, this ultra-luxurious, ultra-pampering bath moisturizes and nourishes skin, while an exclusive aromatherapy blend of essential oils evokes the comfort of warm milk and honey so you can get a good night's sleep.</description>
				<shop_now><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3367509&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Limited%20Editions-_-Shop%20Now%20Warm%20Milk%20%26%20Honey%20Luxe%20Bath]]></shop_now>
				<view_all><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3367515&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Limited%20Editions-_-View%20All%20Limited%20Edition]]></view_all>			
			</product_1>
			<product_2>
				<image>Limited2.swf</image>
				<description header="WARM MILK &amp; HONEY BODY LOTION" url="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3367501&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Limited%20Editions-_-Warm%20Milk%20%26%20Honey%20Body%20Lotion" subtext="">Good night. Cinnamon Essential Oil is comforting. Clove Essential Oil is calming. This ultra-creamy body lotion keeps skin soft and moisturized, while an aromatherapy blend of essential oils evokes the comfort of warm milk and honey so you can get a good night's sleep. In addition, Natural Soybean Oil nourishes and moisturizes, and Glycerin attracts moisture, so skin is beautifully hydrated.</description>
				<shop_now><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3367510&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Limited%20Editions-_-Shop%20Now%20Warm%20Milk%20%26%20Honey%20Body%20Lotion]]></shop_now>
				<view_all><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3367515&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Limited%20Editions-_-View%20All%20Limited%20Edition]]></view_all>
			</product_2>			
			<product_3>
				<image>Limited3.swf</image>
				<description header="WARM MILK &amp; HONEY PILLOW MIST" url="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3367503&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Limited%20Editions-_-Warm%20Milk%20%26%20Honey%20Pillow%20Mist" subtext="">Good night. Cinnamon essential oil is comforting. Clove essential oil is calming. Our aromatherapy blend of essential oils evokes the comfort of warm milk and honey so you can get a good night's sleep.</description>
				<shop_now><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3367511&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Limited%20Editions-_-Shop%20Now%20Warm%20Milk%20%26%20Honey%20Pillow%20Mist]]></shop_now>
				<view_all><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3367515&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Limited%20Editions-_-View%20All%20Limited%20Edition]]></view_all>
			</product_3>

			<view_all>View All Limited Edition</view_all>
		</thumbnail>

		<thumbnail filename="InstantAromatherapy.swf" asset="instant_aromatherapy" image_circle="InstantAroma_Circle.swf">
			<header>INSTANT RELIEF</header>
			<subtext>Pocket-sized Essential Oil blends roll on for relief wherever you go.</subtext>
			<product_1>
				<image>InstantAT1.swf</image>
				<description header="MENTAL CLARITY" url="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3319975&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Instant%20Aromatherapy-_-Mental%20Clarity" subtext="">Mind going a mile a minute. Supposed to be studying. Easily distracted. Thinking about the weekend. Can't concentrate. Long-winded boss. Spaced out. Roll this on for relief. Studies suggest that inhaling Rosemary Essential Oil improves mental clarity and focus. And Lemon Essential Oil is known to improve concentration. </description>
				<shop_now><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3367473&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Instant%20Aromatherapy-_-Shop%20Now%20Mental%20Clarity]]></shop_now>
				<view_all><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3367477&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Instant%20Aromatherapy-_-View%20All%20Instant%20Aromatherapy]]></view_all>			
			</product_1>

			<product_2>
				<image>InstantAT2.swf</image>
				<description header="INSTANT COMFORT" url="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3319977&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Instant%20Aromatherapy-_-Instant%20Comfort" subtext="">Back to school. Long flight. Nervous energy. Anxious about tomorrow. Too much caffeine. Bouncing off the walls. Can't get comfortable. Marathon meeting. Pop quiz. New blemish. The in-laws are visiting. Roll this on for relief. Studies have shown that breathing in Vanilla Absolute eases anxiousness. And Chamomile Essential Oil fosters feelings of comfort.</description>
				<shop_now><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3367474&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Instant%20Aromatherapy-_-Shop%20Now%20Instant%20Comfort]]></shop_now>
				<view_all><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3367477&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Instant%20Aromatherapy-_-View%20All%20Instant%20Aromatherapy]]></view_all>
			</product_2>
			<product_3>
				<image>InstantAT3.swf</image>
				<description header="STAMINA BOOST" url="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3319976&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Instant%20Aromatherapy-_-Stamina%20Boost" subtext="">Working out. Working late. Your turn to make a presentation. Super-rich dessert. Calories to burn. Extra minutes on the elliptical. Car out of gas. Working on the weekends. Impromptu dance contest. The Joneses. Miles to go before you sleep. Roll this on for relief. Studies suggest that inhaling Peppermint helps to maintain vigor and strength. And Lemon essential oil helps to improve alertness. 
</description>
				<shop_now><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3367475&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Instant%20Aromatherapy-_-Shop%20Now%20Stamina%20Boost]]></shop_now>
				<view_all><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3367477&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Instant%20Aromatherapy-_-View%20All%20Instant%20Aromatherapy]]></view_all>
			</product_3>			
			
			<view_all>View All Instant Aromatherapy</view_all>
		</thumbnail>


		<thumbnail filename="Energy.swf" asset="energy" image_circle="Energy_Circle.swf">
			<header>KICK START YOUR DAY</header>
			<subtext>Boost your energy and sharpen your senses.</subtext>
			<product_1>
				<image>Energy1.swf</image>
				<description header="ORANGE GINGER BODY WASH" url="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3319968&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Energy-_-Orange%20Ginger%20Body%20Wash" subtext="">Boost your energy. Orange Essential Oil refreshes and uplifts to relieve tension. Ginger Essential Oil stimulates the soul and sharpens the senses. This nourishing body wash contains Green Tea Extract to help keep skin looking younger and healthier.</description>
				<shop_now><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3366944&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Energy-_-Shop%20Now%20Orange%20Ginger%20Body%20Wash]]></shop_now>
				<view_all><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3367386&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Energy-_-View%20All%20Energy]]></view_all>			
			</product_1>
			<product_2>
				<image>Energy2.swf</image>
				<description header="ORANGE GINGER SUGAR SCRUB" url="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3319969&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Energy-_-Orange%20Ginger%20Sugar%20Scrub" subtext="">Boost your energy. Orange Essential Oil refreshes and uplifts to relieve tension. Ginger Essential Oil stimulates the soul and sharpens the senses. This skin-softening scrub combines exfoliating Sugar and a special moisturizing blend of Sunflower, Safflower, Sweet Almond and Jojoba oils to leave skin silky smooth.</description>
				<shop_now><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3366945&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Energy-_-Shop%20Now%20Orange%20Ginger%20Sugar%20Scrub]]></shop_now>
				<view_all><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3367386&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Energy-_-View%20All%20Energy]]></view_all>
			</product_2>
			<product_3>
				<image>Energy3.swf</image>
				<description header="ORANGE GINGER HAND CREAM" url="http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3319970&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Energy-_-Orange%20Ginger%20Hand%20Cream" subtext="">Boost your energy. Orange Essential Oil refreshes and uplifts to relieve tension. Ginger Essential Oil stimulates the soul and sharpens the senses. This moisturizing hand cream makes hands soft and smooth with a combination of Shea Butter and Murumuru Butter, while natural Borage Oil soothes dry, irritated skin.</description>
				<shop_now><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3366946&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Energy-_-Shop%20Now%20Orange%20Ginger%20Hand%20Cream]]></shop_now>
				<view_all><![CDATA[http://www.bathandbodyworks.com/family/index.jsp?categoryId=3367386&cp=3294363&cm_sp=AT%20Brand%20Shop-_-Zone%202%20-%20Energy-_-View%20All%20Energy]]></view_all>
			</product_3>
			<view_all>View All Energy</view_all>
		</thumbnail>
		
	</carousel>



	<benefits asset_folder="">
		<product thumb="Sleep_Small.png" image="Sleep_Big.png">
			<mainTitle>Stress Relief</mainTitle>
			<body_left title="Relax and refresh.">Peppermint Essential Oil refreshes....</body_left>
			<image>girl_laughs.jpg</image>
			<body_right title="Think clearly.">Eucalyptus Essential Oil clears...</body_right>
		</product>
		<product thumb="Sensuality_Small.png" image="Sensuality_Big.png">
			<mainTitle>Stress Relief</mainTitle>
			<body_left title="Relax and refresh.">Peppermint Essential Oil refreshes....</body_left>
			<image>girl_laughs.jpg</image>
			<body_right title="Think clearly.">Eucalyptus Essential Oil clears...</body_right>
		</product>
		<product thumb="Energy_Small.png" image="Energy_Big.png">
			<mainTitle>Stress Relief</mainTitle>
			<body_left title="Relax and refresh.">Peppermint Essential Oil refreshes....</body_left>
			<image>girl_laughs.jpg</image>
			<body_right title="Think clearly.">Eucalyptus Essential Oil clears...</body_right>
		</product>
		<product thumb="Stress_Small.png" image="Stress_Big.png">
			<mainTitle>Stress Relief</mainTitle>
			<body_left title="Relax and refresh.">Peppermint Essential Oil refreshes....</body_left>
			<image>girl_laughs.jpg</image>
			<body_right title="Think clearly.">Eucalyptus Essential Oil clears...</body_right>
		</product>
	</benefits>


</bbw>


